Another important constraint is the leverage constraints.
另一个重要约束条件是杠杆约束条件
With this constraint, we limit the leverage ratio which, as you recall,
这种约束条件会约束杠杆比率
is the sum of the absolute dollar value of all positions,
杠杆比率等于所有头寸的绝对美元价值之和
long and short, divided by
（包括做多和做空头寸）
whatever actual capital we devote to supporting those positions.
除以这些头寸的实际资本
In our portfolio optimization problem,
在投资组合优化问题中
we work with portfolio weights which are percentages of total invested capital,
我们处理的是投资组合权重 即总投资资本的百分比
so the leverage ratio is just the sum of
所以杠杆比率等于
the absolute value of the weights, long and short.
做多和做空权重的绝对值之和
Again, we discussed this when we discussed alpha factors,
同样 我们在讨论 alpha 因子时讨论过杠杆比率
but the basic idea here is that when you short stocks,
但这里的基本概念是 当你做空股票时
you borrow the stocks and sell them on the open market.
你会借入股票并在开放市场上出售股票
You can use the cash you get to take long positions on other stocks.
你可以利用获得的现金做多其他股票
In general, any investment position is said to
通常 投资头寸如果由债务头寸提供资本
be leveraged if it is financed by a debt position.
则称为杠杆头寸
Whether it's financed by borrowed cash or borrowed stocks.
无论是由借贷的现金还是借贷的股票提供资本
However, it would be much more risky to take
但是 如果用很大的做空头寸
very large short positions in order to finance very large long positions.
对很大的做多头寸提供资本 风险会很高
These are large bets and shorting can be complicated.
这是很大的赌注 做空过程很复杂
If the leverage ratio is allowed to be greater than one,
如果杠杆比率可以大于 1
it means the total magnitude of all year long and short
表示一年的做多和做空头寸的总大小
positions is greater than the amount of initial capital that you have to work with.
大于能够支配的初始资本金额
This means you're borrowing money either by shorting more stocks or by borrowing cash.
表示你在借贷资金 无论是通过做空更多股票还是借贷现金
You have to borrow from somebody and they'll have a maximum there willing to lend to you.
你需要向某人借贷 他们愿意借贷的数额是有上限的
So, you place a constraint on your leverage ratio which is the sum of
所以你对杠杆比率施加约束条件
the absolute values of all your positions to control the scale of this borrowing.
它等于所有头寸的绝对值之和 用于控制借贷规模
This will keep you from ending up in a very extreme leverage position.
可以防止变成非常极端的杠杆头寸
If you're using an objective function like
如果你使用这样的目标函数
this and you are not using a risk constraint like this,
并且没有使用这样的风险约束条件
you need a constraint like
则需要杠杆约束条件等约束条件
the leverage constraint to keep your weights from growing to infinity.
来防止权重变成无穷值
You can try to control leverage by just controlling risk,
你可以尝试仅通过控制风险来控制杠杆
but the leverage constraint is usually
但是杠杆约束条件通常是硬性约束条件
a hard constraint that will also be necessary to enforce.
有必要施加杠杆约束条件